# **ELLIS LEE**

#### USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

#### SUMMARY

Current Undergraduate student at UC San Diego majoring in Cognitive Science Human-Computer Interaction and minoring in Design who showcases exceptional organization and communication skills and is dedicated to hard work. Invested in gaining professional experience and pursuing a career in the field of UX Research and Design.

### CONTACT

+916 990 3173

ellisylee@gmail.com

www.ellisylee.com

## SKILLS

Microsoft Office

Sketch

Spanish

HTML CSS

Adobe Illustrator

Java • • • •

#### **EXPERIENCE**

SEDS UCSD, Graphic Designer

FEB 2017 - PRESENT

Developed marketing materials for successful Indiegogo campaign (logos, infographics, and presentations)

UCSF Brain Imaging Study, Research Assistant
NOV 2016 - PRESENT

Screened and scheduled subjects to come in for interview, fMRI scan, and physiological data collection

Administer neuropsychological tests (CDRS-R, RADS-2, BDI-II, MADRS, CDI, MASC, CGAS, etc) for depression and/or anxiety

The Office of Admissions, College Ambassador
JAN 2016 - PRESENT

Led informative and entertaining campus tours to diverse groups of prospective students and their families to promote UC San Diego and create an enjoyable guest experience.

Managed front desk operations by answering and triaging phone calls, writing emails, assisting walk-ins, entering data, and sending mail on behalf of the university.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of California San Diego JUN 2019 - JAN 2020

Bachelor of Science in Cognitive Science Human-Computer Interaction